她又给我发短信了  哥们
She's texting me again, bro.
-谁  -安吉
- Who? - Angie.
怎么  你又要见她吗
What? Are you gonna see her again?
不  我得拒绝她
Nah, man. I have to shut that down.
你念叨这女人几个月了
You've been singing the blues about this woman for months.
她向你伸出手  你又要打开她吗
She reaches her hand out, and you're gonna slap it away?
她伤了我的心
Yeah, well, she broke my heart, man.
所以  该再给她个机会
Hey, which means she deserves another shot.
相信我
Trust me.
我了解的  我这都14年了
I know -- 14 years and counting.
你是对的
You're right.
我会给她打电话的
I'll give her a call.
很好
Nice.
我去拿其他的袋子
I'm gonna go get the rest of the bags.
不是我
That wasn't me.
拿着剃刀一般尖利的法国吐司和
Says the guy with the razor-sharp French toast
香肠烤串的人如是说
and the sausage kabob.
好吧  是我  但是气球自找的
Okay, that was me, but that balloon had it coming.
敬你  我的爱人  我的心肝  我的新娘
To you, my love, my heart, my bride.
欢迎回我们家
Welcome back to our home.
太有爱了
Oh, that is so sweet, Castle.
但这怎么能算欢迎我回来
But how is this really a welcome back
我每晚都偷偷溜进来
if I've been sneaking into your room almost every night?
因为你正式把东西都搬回来了
Well, because you officially moved all your stuff back in.
既然我们说好一起寻找洛克塞特的下落
Now that we've agreed to hunt LokSat together,
我们可以继续之前的工作了
we can simply pick up exactly where we left off.
我记得  我们今早就在这里
And as I recall, we left off this morning somewhere
停下了
right about here.
露西  关音乐
Lucy, music off!
好的  里克
As you wish, Rick.
搞什么
What just happened?
我把露西内嵌进了公寓基建中
Well, I've integrated Lucy into all the loft's infrastructure.
气温  灯光  音乐  什么都归她管
Climate, lights, music -- you name it, she controls it.
只是有些小问题要调整
Just got to work out a few kinks.
有些事我还是喜欢用老法子
Well, I still like a few things the old-fashioned way,
要我去给你泡杯咖啡吗
so do you want me to make you a cup of coffee?
不必  凯特
Uh, no need, Kate.
我已经按里克的喜好编程了咖啡机
I've programmed Rick's coffee exactly to his liking --
古巴咖啡  蒸牛奶  两块糖  少许肉豆蔻
Cuban blend, steamed milk, two sugars, pinch of nutmeg.
很棒吧
Amazing, huh?
不  里克  你才是最棒的
No, Rick, you're amazing.
不  你最棒了
No, you are.
-不  你最棒了  -不  露西  你最棒了
- No, you are. - No, Lucy, you are.
-里克  你最棒了  你知道的  -贝克特
- Rick, you are amazing, and you know it. - Beckett.
别说了  我不要再跟你争了
Stop it. I'm not doing this with you again.
-你才别说了  -好的  知道
- You stop it. - Yeah. Got it.
我们有案子
We have a homicide.
你  我  犯罪现场  这才是天意
You, me, and a crime scene -- just as nature intended.
好了  警监  我们走
All right, Captain, let's roll.
不行
Yeah, no can do.
警监得一心多用
Captains have to multitask.
其实  我要去跟地检官见面
In fact, I am due for a meeting with the D.A.
你去跟男生们汇合吧
So why don't you meet up with the boys?
稍后跟我汇报案情
We can debrief later.
好的
You got it.
露西  你能给我做杯咖啡吗
Um, Lucy, do you think you could make me a cup of coffee --
少许低脂牛奶  两块善品糖
splash of low-fat milk, two Splendas?
不行啊  没有善品糖了
No can do. All out of Splenda.
但离这儿两个街区有家星巴克
But there is a Starbucks two blocks from here.
需要指路吗
Would you like directions?
不了  谢谢
No. Thanks.
我知道在哪
I know where it is.
好啊  祝你愉快  再见
Great. Have fun. Goodbye.
请离开吧
Leave the house.
蕾妮  看谁来了
Lanie, look who's here.
卡塞尔  很高兴你和贝克特破镜重圆了
Castle! So happy you and Beckett are back together.
帮个忙  别再跟她闹翻了
Now do us all a favor and don't mess things up with her again.
你为什么认定是我不对
Why do you assume it was my fault?
什么事都是你不对
Everything is your fault.
这位是新被害人  麦克·科比  一枪毙命
Now come meet our new victim -- Michael Kirby, single GSW.
窃贼/凶手用绳索从那个空调风口下来
Our thief/killer rappelled from that A/C duct.
而且盗走了十万现金
And they got away with $100,000 in cash.
这位是达伦·艾夫斯
This is Darren Ives.
听到枪声时他在里面
He was inside when he heard the shot.
冲出来时凶手已经逃了
Rushed out, but the killer was already gone.
我不知道他怎么做到的
I don't know how that guy did it.
这是一家安保严密的仓库
I mean, this is a high-security warehouse.
简直赶上诺克斯堡了
It's damn near Fort Knox.
你没发现任何异常吗
And you didn't see anything suspicious?
没有  就是一次普通的任务
Nothing. It was just a normal drop.
我们来这边给你录口供吧
Let's finish taking your statement over here, please.
怎么  你又过敏了吗
What? Are your allergies acting up?
这是什么  明胶吗
What is this -- gelatin?
闻着像女士香水
It smells like ladies perfume.
那是什么味儿  白钻石吗
What is that scent? Is that White Diamonds?
不  香奈儿五号
No. Chanel No. 5.
单向乐队身体喷雾  搞定
One Direction body spray. Nailed it.
是从空调风口滴下来的
This stuff dripped from the A/C vent.
鉴证组取了样本
CSU took samples --
是管道内的警报传感器上的
it's from the alarm sensors in the vent.
凶手用这东西解除了警报系统
Apparently, the killer used it to disable the security system.
蕾妮  你能叫实验室加急分析一下吗
Lanie, can you ask the lab to put a rush on this?
怎么了
Why? What is it?
我见过这种手法
I've seen this M.O. before.
那是十年前了
It was like 10 years ago.
是你在54分局工作时遇到的吗
So, when you worked with the 54th?
对  我抓到了一个贼
Yeah. I collared a thief.
名叫索尼娅·鲁伊兹
Her name was, uh, Sonia Ruiz.
她所在的团伙
She was part of a crew
从一家拍卖行偷走了价值
that stole $10 million worth of gold coins
一千万的金币
from some auction house.
他们也用了芳香明胶吗
And they used a fragrant gel, too?
是用果冻和女士香水调和的混合物
It was actually a unique blend of Jell-O and ladies perfume.
你是说用儿童甜品跟淡香水混合
You're saying a kid's dessert mixed with eau de toilette
能挫败一套复杂的安保系统
can foil a sophisticated security system?
相信我  我们需要养只狗
I'm telling you, we need a dog.
那配方好使吗
Does that formula even work?
是的  是团伙里一个人想出来的
Yeah. Someone in the crew came up with it.
明胶能阻挡安保激光
The gelatin blocks the security lasers,
而香水中的邻苯二甲酸盐
and the phthalates in the perfume
使其在传感器上均衡分布
create an even distribution over the sensors.
但混合物百分比得刚刚好
But the mix has to be exact --
80%的果冻  20%的香水
80% Jell-O, 20% perfume.
而这正是在
Which is the precise ratio
犯罪现场发现的明胶的混合比
of the gelatin found at our crime scene.
实验室发来了分析报告
Lab sent over the analysis report.
跟九年前的劫案中使用的一样
Identical to the heist from nine years ago,
当时唯一抓到的罪犯就是索尼娅·鲁伊兹
where the only perp captured was Sonia Ruiz.
没错  就是她
Yep. That's her.
那么这显然不是巧合
So, obviously, this wasn't a coincidence.
很可能是团伙中的一个人
Most likely, someone from the crew
重新开始使用这项手段  并杀了人
reused the technique and is behind our victim's murder.
不可能是索尼娅
Well, it couldn't have been Sonia.
她被判了15年
She got 15 years.
团伙其余人呢
And what about the rest of the crew?
她没有说出任何人
Nah, she didn't give up any names.
据传这帮人是一个神秘的
The rumor was that the crew was put together
老大人物纠集到一起的
by some mysterious shot-caller --
外号叫"大白鲨"
goes by the street name of "Great White."
能不能靠被盗金币追踪他们
Is it possible to trace them through the stolen gold coins?
他们总是要卖的嘛
I mean, they had to have tried to sell them at some point.
劫案之后他们没有任何消息
There hasn't been any trace of them since the heist.
这也有道理
Well, that makes sense.
如果他们把金币融化取金子
If they melted the coins down for the gold,
那么就无从追踪金币了
that would render the coins untraceable.
埃斯波  我们去看看索尼娅·鲁伊兹吧
Espo, why don't we pay Sonia Ruiz a little visit?
她或许当年没有背叛她的团伙
She might not have turned on her crew back in the day,
但都蹲了九年监狱了
but after nine years hard time,
我们或许能说服她
we might be able to persuade her.
我记得
You know what? From what I remember,
她可能是那种记仇的人
she may be the type to hold a grudge,
或许你带卡塞尔去可能更容易突破
so you might have better luck taking Castle with you.
不要  我可不要再中这个计了
Oh, no, not falling for that trick again.
跟你们三个骗我的不同
Contrary to what you three led me to believe,
女子监狱跟
those women's prisons are nothing like
深夜电影里的完全不同  你们好好玩吧
the late-night Skinemax movies, so have fun.
好了  鲁伊兹小姐  把你知道的告诉我
All right, Ms. Ruiz, tell me what you know.
得了  我当年没告密
Please. I didn't snitch back in the day.
我现在为什么要告密
Why would I start now?
因为九年前只是一起劫案
Because nine years ago, this was just a burglary,
而现在成了杀人案
and now it's a murder.
杀人案
Murder?
谁死了
Who died?
一位押运车司机
An armored truck driver.
索尼娅  你帮我  我帮你
Look, Sonia, you help me out, I'll help you out.
怎么帮
With what?
我三个月后就能假释了
I'm up for parole in three months,
由于监狱人满为患  我肯定能出去了
and due to overcrowding, I'm a lock to get out.
除非我去你的假释听证会上
Not if I go to your parole hearing
说你不肯在一桩凶杀案侦破中配合警方工作
and testify that you refused to cooperate in solving a homicide.
就这样吗
It's like that?
我的停尸房里有个无辜的男人
I've got an innocent man in the morgue
现在留下了一妻两子
who left behind a wife and two small kids,
是的  就是这样
so, yeah, it's like that.
我想帮你也帮不到
I couldn't help you even if I wanted to.
大白鲨安排的金币劫案
The gold coin heist Great White set up
是两人合作的
was a two-person job,
但我不知道我搭档的名字
but I don't know my partner's name.
这没道理
That doesn't make any sense.
就是这样
And yet it's true.
他不知道我的名字  我也不知道他的
He didn't know my name, and I didn't know his.
这样我们都不能供出彼此
So neither one of us could rat out the other.
我们都叫鲨鱼  我是条纹鲨  他是锤头鲨
We used shark names. I was Mako. He was Hammerhead.
好吧  关于大白鲨  你知道什么
All right. What can you tell me about Great White?
我知道他的名字  吉米·桑切斯
Now, his name I knew -- Jimmy Sanchez.
他当年在我们那一带是个老大
He was the neighborhood shot-caller back in the day.
好吧  我能去哪找他
Okay, so, where can I find him?
墓地
In the cemetery.
他三年多前死了
He died a little over three years ago.
等等  如果大白鲨死了
Wait, if Great White is dead,
那么锤头鲨极可能就是凶手了
then Hammerhead's most likely our killer.
那个果冻香水的配方就是他发明的
Hey, that Jell-O perfume formula was his invention,
肯定是他
so it has to be.
关于锤头鲨  你都记得什么
W-What do you remember about Hammerhead?
什么都行
Anything at all.
他有次说漏嘴  他跟吉米·桑切斯
Once let it slip that he met Jimmy Sanchez
是在一家叫斗牛士的酒吧认识的
at a bar called, um, El Toro.
很好  我会让我的警探去那儿看看
Good. I'll have my detectives head off over there.
祝你好运  女士
Good luck with that, lady.
那是在西班牙哈莱姆
It's up in Spanish Harlem.
那里的人是不会对警察开口的
No one there talks to the police.
但他们会跟我开口
However, they will talk to me.
你想要我放你出去
You want me to put you on the street?
不行
No.
是你拿假释威胁我
Hey, you're hanging parole over my head.
你想抓锤头鲨  就得这么抓
You want Hammerhead, this is how you get him.
监狱部门准许她休假了
The Department of Corrections authorized her furlough?
是的  现在  索尼娅是我们最佳也是唯一
Yeah. Right now, Sonia is our best and only path
查清锤头鲨真实身份的办法
to Hammerhead's real identity.
打算怎么办
So, what's the plan?
你和埃斯波要去
You and Espo are gonna head over to the...
抱歉
Excuse me.
怎么回事
What's going on?
你有什么瞒着我
What are you not telling me?
-说来好笑  -怎么了
- So, funny story, really, uh... - What?
索尼娅和我  我们有一腿
Sonia and I were, uh, we were kind of involved.
约会吗
Involved like dating?
约会  才不是
Dating? No.
拜托  约会
Come on. Dating.
我们是订婚了
We -- We were more like engaged.
订婚  你...
Engaged?! You were --
等等  你这么多年都没告诉我
Wait a second. All these years you never told me that?
你没问过
You never asked.
你是个警察  怎么会跟一个罪犯搞上
You're a cop. How could you get involved with a criminal?
严格讲  他们都在一行里混
Well, technically, they were in the same line of work.
所以可以算是办公室恋情
So, really, it's a workplace romance.
多谢了
Thank you.
我起初并不知道她是罪犯
I didn't know she was a crook at first, okay?
我在一家夜店认识了她  她看上去挺正常的
I-I met her at a club. She seemed normal.
我们十分合拍
We just -- We just clicked.
或许正因如此  她才没告诉我她的真面目
And it's probably why she hid who she really was from me.
你什么时候得知真相的
A-And when did you find out the truth?
已经太晚的时候
After it was too late!
我们都订婚了 她突然开始怪怪的
We were engaged, and then she started acting strange --
莫名其妙地消失不见
disappearing at odd hours,
不能直视我的眼睛
and then she couldn't look me in the eye.
金币失窃的消息一出来
And then news of that gold coin heist broke, and I - - -
我说不清  我就是猜到了
I don't know. I knew.
是我逮捕了她
And I was the one who arrested her.
你有把戒指要回来吗
So, did you ask for the ring back,
还是留给她了  让她在监狱里
or did you let her keep that so she could trade it
拿来换烟抽
for cigarettes in the prison yard?
我...别回答了
That's -- Don't answer that.
好吧  那么这次你显然不能插手了
Okay. So, obviously, you're sitting this one out.
为什么要让我坐冷板凳
Why are you benching me?
好吧  我明白  但没必要
Okay. I get it. But there's no need.
我曾经对她有的感情
Any feelings I had for her
都在我给她戴上手铐的一刻消失了
died the moment I slapped those cuffs on.
相信我  我完全忘记她了
Trust me, I am over her completely.
哈维尔
Javier?
你确定你忘记她了
You sure you're over her?
你最好告诉你的嘴巴一声  闭上吧
You might want to tell your mouth. Close that up.
她好美
She's gorgeous.
她还行
She a'ight.
你还好吗
Are you all right?
你刚看见她时
I mean, you seemed a little taken aback
似乎有点震惊
when you first saw her.
没有  就是...
Nah, man. It's just, um --
就是有点往日重现
it's just a little deja Vu.
她穿着我逮捕她时的那套衣服
She's literally wearing the same outfit I arrested her in.
九年了  衣服还是那么美
Nine years later, still a great dress.
那是一个周五的晚上
It was a Friday night.
你说什么
What's that?
那是一个周五的晚上
It was a Friday night.
我们每周五晚上去跳莎莎舞
We went salsa dancing on Friday nights.
哈维尔  承认你对她还有感觉
You know, Javier, there's no shame in admitting
并没有什么丢人的
if you still have feelings.
我知道  但我对她没有感觉了
I know, but I don't.
她就是个罪犯  就是这样
She's just another convict -- nothing else.
这个脚踝监视器是最新的设备
This ankle monitor is a next-generation device
有很多新的追踪功能
with a variety of new tracking features.
这是操作说明书
This is the instruction manual.
我可以教你一些它的功能
Now, I could walk you through some of the features --
他跟这事有什么关系
What does he have to do with this?
莱恩警探会陪你去酒吧
Uh, Detective Ryan's gonna accompany you to the bar he's --
什么  他  绝对不要
What? Him? Hell, no.
把我带回监狱吧  这事成不了
Take me back to prison. This is not gonna work.
等等  哪里有问题吗
Wait, I-I'm sorry. What's the problem?
你要把我送进一个西班牙哈莱姆酒吧
You're gonna send me into a Spanish Harlem bar
还带着一个警察
with Saint Paddy on my arm.
亲爱的  我以前做过卧底
Sweetheart, I used to work undercover.
我能顾好我自己
I can take care of myself.
听着  这件事唯一的解决方法是
Look, the only way this is gonna work
我跟一个能够融入其中的人一起去
is if I go in with somebody who can blend in.
一个哈维那样的人
Someone like Javi.
第无数次跟你说  贝克特  我能搞定
For the umpteenth time, Beckett, I -- I can handle this.
真的  因为如果是我
Really? Because if it was me,
我不觉得我能这么自信
I don't think I would be that confident.
这确实会很尴尬
Is it awkward? Of course.
但是这是我们解决这起谋杀案的唯一方法
But it's the only way we're gonna solve this murder.
卡塞尔和莱恩会在后面的车里支援我
Castle and Ryan are gonna be backing me up in a follow car.
最坏能发生什么呢
What's the worst that could happen?
我不知道
I don't know.
这才是我紧张的原因
And that's what makes me nervous.
凯特  我不会让你失望的
Kate, I am not gonna let you down.
好吧  听着  索尼娅
All right. Listen up, Sonia.
我说什么  你就做什么  明白了吗
You do what I say when I say it, understand?
我也很高兴见到你  亲爱的
Nice to see you too, sweetie.
我没有在跟你开玩笑  好吗
This is not a -- this is not a joke, okay?
当我说跳的时候  你说
When I say "Jump," You say --
如果你觉得我会穿着
That you're out of your damn mind
这双高跟鞋跳的话  你一定是疯了
if you think I'm jumping in these heels, okay?
既然说到了  我需要新衣服
And speaking of, I need new clothes
因为这身已经买了快10年了
'cause this outfit is damn near 10 years old.
我要维护我的名誉  所以我得看到标签
And I got a rep to protect, so I need labels.
行  随便  我们赶紧把这件事解决
Fine, whatever. Let's just hurry up and get this over with.
以前你晚上兴奋的时候
Didn't I used to say that to you
我不是总对你说这个吗
whenever you got frisky at night?
我们走吧
Let's go.
这件事要好玩了
This is gonna be so much fun.
麻烦你能快点吗
Can you please speed up?
等我们到那
You know, my prison term is gonna be over
我牢都该坐完了
by the time we get there.
这里有限速
I'm going the speed limit.
太好了
Oh, good.
我可不希望有警察叫你靠边停车
You know, I don't want you to get pulled over by a cop.
拜托  快一点
Come on! Hurry up!
我觉得我们最好速度再慢一点
I think we better slow down a little bit.
就这样
There we go.
这样好多了
That's much better.
我还是不敢相信哈维以前跟这女人订婚了
I still can't believe Javi was engaged to that woman.
我能想象
Oh, I can.
你看到他们两个之间的来电了吗
I mean, you see the electricity between those two?
都能听到电火花声了
It crackles.
是啊  这可能是个问题
Yeah, that might be a problem.
我们得盯着她
We need to keep an eye on her.
实际上  我觉得我们能做更多
Well, actually, I think we can do more than that.
索尼娅的脚踝监控器里有窃听装备
There a listening device built in to Sonia's ankle monitor.
-一个隐藏麦克风  -对
- A hidden mike? - Yeah.
我们只需要把安全代码输进这个应用
All we have to do is enter the security number into the app --
我们就能听见他们说什么了
we can hear everything they're saying.
但他们不会知道我们在偷听
But they wouldn't know that we were listening.
这是对他们隐私的侵犯
That would be an invasion of their privacy.
你觉得这样有问题吗
You got a problem with that?
不  不
No! No.
你知道  我很高兴
You know, I'm glad
你没有因为罪恶感而发胖
you didn't get fat over all that guilt.
什么罪恶感
What guilt?
举报我的罪恶感
For turning me in.
我为什么要为履行职责而有罪恶感
Why would I feel guilty about doing my job?
因为你爱我
Because you love me.
我爱过你
Loved you.
过去时  很久以前
Past tense -- way past.
结束了  完了  终结了
Done. Finished. Terminado.
你知道  我一直想跟你说谢谢
You know, I was meaning to say thank you.
为了什么
For what?
你逮捕了我
For arresting me.
你把我从要跟你多待一天的痛苦中拯救了
You saved me the misery of spending another day with you.
太残忍了
That's harsh.
你奶奶的髋关节怎么样了
How's your abuelita's hip?
挺好的  她终于换了一个新的
Good. She finally got it replaced.
那就好
Oh, good.
她人一直很好
She was always so sweet.
你全家人都是
Your whole family was.
这也是我不安的原因
That's what haunts me, you know --
想着他们
thinking how
得知我不过是个罪犯时
they must have reacted when they learned
会作何反应
I was nothing more than a crook.
如果大白鲨是在这里遇到锤头鲨
If Great White met Hammerhead here,
肯定有人知道他的真实身份
stands to reason that somebody knows his real identity.
是啊  但那是9年前了
Yeah, but that was nine years ago.
我们从哪开始
Where do we start?
从酒保开始
The bartender.
他肯定知道原来的人去哪了
He's bound to know where the old timers are.
对吗
Yeah?
对
Yeah.
让我来跟他说
Let me do the talking.
好啊  伙计们  想喝点什么
What's going on, guys? What can I get for you?
龙舌兰  双份
Uh, shot of tequila, double rows.
什么
What?
双份来了
Double rows coming up.
谢谢  亲爱的
Thank you, baby.
她在干什么
What is she doing?
她在融入她的环境
She's blending in to her environment.
这实际上是个很聪明的策略
It's actually a brilliant strategy.
或者她只是想让哈维喝醉
Either that or getting Javier drunk.
她为什么要那么做
Why would she want to do that?
是啊  就是啊
Exactly. Exactly.
叮  叮
Ding ding.
赢家出现了
We got a winner.
再给我们来一杯
Set us up again.
如果你想的话
If you say so.
兄弟  你在这做酒保多长时间了
Hey, bro, how long you been bartending here?
10年多
A little over 10 years.
那你应该记得一个叫吉米·桑切斯的人
Oh, so then you remember a guy named Jimmy Sanchez?
人送外号大白鲨
went by the name of Great White?
大白鲨  是的  你怎么问起他了
Great White. Yeah, yeah. Why you ask?
你有没有见过他跟
Did you ever see him with this, you know,
这一带一个挺好看的孩子在一起
really good-looking kid form the neighborhood --
个子不高  有胡子
short with a beard?
没见过  抱歉
No, sorry.
没关系
Hey, it's all good.
我刚假释出来
I just got out on parole, you know,
以前犯了点事被关起来了
from a little job I did back in the day,
要是我能找到他的话
so if I could just find him...
小姐  我帮不了你
Look, senorita, I can't help you out.
现在呢
How 'bout now?
你干什么  哥们
What the hell are you doing, bro?
告诉我他的名字
Give me his name.
等一下  他是不是在
Wait, does this sound like --
听上去他是在跟酒保
It sounds like he's playing "Five Finger Fillet"
玩剁手指  是的
with the bartender, it certainly does.
别跟贝克特说
Don't tell Beckett.
我的手快抽筋了  哥们
My hand's getting twitchy, bro.
你最好告诉我
You better tell me something.
好吧
Okay.
他叫乔伊
Look, it's J-Joey.
行了吧  他的名字叫乔伊
All right? His name's Joey.
姓什么
Joey what?
我真不知道
It beats the hell out of me, man.
我已经有一年多没见过他了
I haven't seen the guy in over a year.
-我就知道这么多  -我不信
- That's all I know. - I don't belive you.
住手
Stop!
他跟他祖母关系很好
He's close with his grandmother.
她就住在这条街上
She lives up the street.
第三座楼  砖房  6D
Third building, the brick one, 6D.
她能告诉你他在哪
She can tell you where he is.
谢谢
Thank you.
6D
6D.
门开着
It's open.
有人吗
Hello?
卡塞尔
Castle.
没信号了
I lost the signal.
你敢动我就宰了你
You make a move, and I'll kill you.
你是谁  你为什么闯进我祖母的家里
Who are you, and why'd you break into my GG's house?
-把枪放下  -去你妈
- Put the gun down. - Screw that.
通常我会耐心地劝你
Normally I'd do this back and forth thing with you,
不过我得去追她  所以
but I got to go chase her, so...
-伙计  -老实待着
- Man... - Don't go anywhere.
好了  有了
Okay. Here we go.
再输入一遍序列号
Just re-enter the serial number...
搞定
and voil?
这是我的脚趾  我愿意抠就抠
They're my toes, and I can pick them if I want.
不是这个电子脚镣
That's the wrong ankle monitor.
肯定是搞错数了
Must have transposed their number.
那不是
Was that...?
该死
Damn it!
-是的  她就在那  -看我的
- Yeah, she's right there. - I got her.
索尼娅  站住
Sonia! Stop!
哈维  你没事吗
Javi, you okay?
是的  我没事  你在干嘛
Yeah, I'm okay. What are you doing?
那个人拿着把猎枪
There was a guy with a shotgun --
把手拿出来
Let me see your hands!
什么
What?
怎么  你觉得我是要逃跑吗
What, you think I was trying to escape?
我看见了枪  所以我就跑了
I see a gun, and I run!
我是想找电话报警
I was trying to get to a phone to call 911.
我才不信呢  宝贝
Not buying it, sweetheart.
爱尔兰人
Irish,
我的刑期只剩三个月了  好吧
I got three months left on my sentence, okay?
我已经服刑了九年了
I already served nine long years.
如果我现在跑的话  还会再加两年
I run right now, they add another two.
你觉得我有那么蠢吗
How dumb do you think I am?
别回答  这是个陷阱
Don't answer that. It's a trap, trust me.
你觉得她说的是真话吗
Do you think she's telling the truth?
我不知道
I don't know.
她之前也骗过我
It's not like she hasn't lied to me before.
我去
Damn.
我就知道你还喜欢我
I knew you weren't over me.
我早就忘了你了
I am so over you.
刚才那个用枪指着我的是不是锤头鲨
Now, was that Hammerhead that jumped me with the shotgun?
是的  就是他
Yeah. That was him.
听我说  我刚才不知道你是警察
Look, I didn't know you were a cop, man.
你闯入了我祖母的家
You broke into my GG's apartment,
我的猎枪是注册过的
my shotgun is registered,
而且我有权利保护自己的家
and I have a right to defend my property.
所以你们没有理由抓我
So y'all got nothing to hold me on.
你喜欢鲨鱼吗  乔伊
You like sharks, Joey?
是的  我觉得还行吧
Yeah. They're cool, I guess.
你最喜欢什么鲨鱼
What's your favorite shark?
我喜欢那种
Oh, yeah, I like the ones with the,
头的形状很奇怪的那种
with the funny shaped heads.
你知道我说的那种吧
You know what I'm talking about?
是的  锤头鲨
Oh, yeah, the hammerheads.
是的  就那种
Yeah, that's -- that's it.
很有意思  因为
That's funny because,
我们听说你就是锤头鲨
we heard that you were Hammerhead.
是吗  谁跟你们说的
Yeah? Who told you that?
等一下  之前跟你一起的那个女孩
Wait, that girl that was with you earlier.
我就说她看着面熟嘛
I knew she looked familiar.
锤头鲨一般不杀人的  乔伊
Hammerheads aren't usually man-killers, Joey.
这是怎么回事
So, what happened?
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
十年前  你曾是一个抢劫团伙成员
10 years ago, you were part of a heist crew
利用明胶和香水混合物
that used gelatin mixed with perfume
使安保系统瘫痪
to disable security systems.
昨晚  你用了同样的办法
Last night, you used the same recipe
闯入了一家安保严密的仓库
to break into a high-security warehouse.
只是这次  你被发现了  并杀死了保安
Only thing is, you got caught and you murdered a guard.
昨晚  我在泽西
Last night, I was in Jersey
在我的鸡鸡鸡店
at my Chicken-Chicken-Chicken.
是一家做鸡肉的餐厅
It's a chicken restaurant.
我在三州地区开了七家
I own seven in the Tri-State area.
我猜一下  你是用
Let me guess -- you bought those
抢来的金币买下的
with your share of the gold coin heist?
就算是的  诉讼时效也已经过了
Even if I did, statute of limitations is over.
而且我有很多证人能够证明
And I have a dozen witnesses that put me
我在鸡鸡鸡店待到凌晨三点
at the Chicken-Chicken-Chicken until 3:00 A.M.
所以  这事你也告不倒我的
So, you ain't gonna touch me with that score either.
这并不意味着你没有参与抢劫
That doesn't mean you weren't a part of the heist.
否则他们怎么会知道明胶配方呢
How else would they know about the gelatin formula?
简单  因为不光我一个人知道
Easy -- I ain't the only one who knew it.
大白鲨
Great White?
吉米·桑切斯已经死了
Jimmy Sanchez is dead.
我们确认过了
We confirmed that.
是的  可是他还带过别的人
Yeah, but he ran other crews.
谁知道他告诉过多少人
Ain't no telling how many of them he told.
我现在是个成功的商人了
Look, I'm a successful businessman now.
好吧  我的那些犯罪冲动
All right? Whatever criminal instincts I had...
早就过去了
long gone.
我现在只做鸡肉
I'm all about the chicken now.
警监
Hey, Cap.
乔伊的不在场证明核实了
Joey's alibi checks out.
我们正在详细调查他的财务状况
We're pulling apart his financials,
但看起来他似乎说的是实话
but it looks like he might be telling the truth.
好  我让警员带索尼娅回监狱了
Okay. I got UNIs taking Sonia back to prison.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
我就是...
Yeah, I'm just, uh, you know...
很遗憾这条路没什么结果
I'm just bummed that it didn't work out.
不是我和索尼娅
Not -- Not between me and Sonia.
我是在说这个案子
I'm talking about the -- the case.
莱恩  你有什么发现吗
Ryan! You got something?
我觉得那伙人有内应
Yeah. I think that crew used an inside man.
什么  你为什么这么觉得
What? What makes you think that?
那个戒备森严的仓库的安保系统
The security system at that high-security warehouse
远比丢失金子的拍卖行的
is way more sophisticated than the auction house
复杂得多
where those gold coins were stolen.
他们有红外热像仪
I mean, they had an infrared camera system
没技术含量的旁门左道根本不可能攻破
that some low-tech bypass couldn't have knocked out.
但是系统在谋杀发生的时候停止运作了
Yet it was down at the time of the murder.
所以  是有内部的人把它关了
So, somebody on the inside did turn it off.
没错  麦克·科比  被害人
Yes. Michael Kirby, our victim.
解除系统用的是他的安全码
His security code was the one used.
但如果他参与其中  为什么杀他
But if he was in on it, then why kill him?
我不知道  但我们可以问他的妻子
I don't know. But we could ask his wife.
警监  我想
Hey, Captain, I'd like to, uh,
自愿带索尼娅回监狱
volunteer to take Sonia back to the prison.
不行  我不觉得这是个好主意
No. I don't think that's a good idea.
我知道  但这样做才是对的
Yeah, I know, but it's the right thing to do.
好吧
All right.
你去询问科比的妻子
You interview Kirby's wife.
我要你明天一早回来
And I expect you back first thing in the morning,
准备工作
ready to work.
是  长官
Yes, ma'am.
他没问题的
He's gonna be fine.
我送她  兄弟们
I'll take her, boys --
警监的命令
Captain's orders.
这真扯  哈维  你知道我可以继续帮忙的
This is bull, Javi. You know I can still help.
我很抱歉  乔伊是你唯一的机会
I'm sorry. Joey was your only shot.
真见鬼
This sucks.
我以为我至少能
I thought I'd at least get...
吃顿像样的晚餐  或者洗个热水澡
a decent meal, maybe a hot shower,
睡一睡真正的床
sleep in a real bed.
还有三个月  你就能享受这一切了
Well, in three months, you'll get all that.
你不明白
You don't understand.
九年  我吃着牢饭
Nine years, I've eaten prison food,
睡着一块六英寸厚的海绵
slept on a six-inch piece of foam.
九年  我活得提心吊胆
Nine years, I've had to live on edge.
我以为我能有点时间放松
And I thought I'd get, you know, a little time to relax.
车程有一个小时
Well, the drive is an hour.
你可以在车上放松
You can relax in the car.
最新美剧下载
www.ZiMuZu.tv
为什么叫我来这里
What am I doing here?
我已经录过口供了
I already gave my statement.
科比太太  我们已经知道
Mrs. Kirby, we know about
你丈夫参与了这次抢劫
your husband's involvement in the heist.
什么
What?
我们找到了总计一万美金
We found anonymous bank deposits
存入你们联名账户的
totaling $10,000
匿名银行存款
made to your joint account.
我们可以以从犯罪起诉你
We can charge you as an accessory.
我丈夫遇到了麻烦
My husband was in trouble.
他向一些坏人借了钱
He borrowed money from some bad people,
而我们还不起
and we couldn't pay it back.
然后上周  有个人来找他
And then last week, a man came to him,
那人说如果我丈夫帮他做事
and he said he could make the debt go away
他就能让那笔债务消失
if my husband would help him.
这男人叫什么  他长什么样
What was this man's name? What did he look like?
我不知道  我从没见过他
I don't know. I never met him.
我只知道麦克用他藏在车库的
All I know is that Michael communicated
一部预付款手机和他联系
on a pre-paid cellphone he kept in the garage.
-那部手机还在吗  -嗯
- Is the phone still there? - Yeah.
我们要干什么
What are we doing?
-这是你妈妈的房子  -嗯
- This is your mom's house. - Yeah.
今天是周四  家庭聚餐的日子
It's Thursday, family dinner night.
你能吃上一顿家常菜
You're gonna have a home cooked meal,
然后直接回监狱
and then it's straight back to the prison.
我无法面对你的家人  哈维
I can't face your family, Javi,
他们已经知道我是什么样的人了
not after what they know about me.
我什么都没告诉他们
I didn't tell them anything.
什么
What?
我告诉他们是我搞砸了
I told them that I was the one that screwed up,
你和我分手了
that you broke up with me.
你是为我才这么做的
You did that for me?
谢谢
Thank you.
来吧
All right.
好啊
Hello.
亲爱的  你迟到了
Mijo, you're late!
你知道我会担心的
You know how I worry.
打个电话有多难
How hard is it to call?
堵车  来  过来
The traffic -- come here. Come here.
最近怎样  表哥  还在为他们卖命吗
'Sup, cuz? Still selling out to the man?
你还住在你妈妈的地下室里吗
Are you still living in your mama's basement?
-索尼娅  是你吗  -是又如何
- Sonia? Is that you? - Yeah, whatever.
你们两个又在一起了吗
So, are you two back together?
不不  我们没在一起
No. No. We are not together.
埃斯笨蛋
Estopido!
别再让她离开你了
Don't let this one get away twice.
快来  吃饭了
Come. Eat, eat.
我做了哈维尔的最爱  莫封戈
I made Javier's favorite -- mofongo.
你是个幸运的男人  哈维
You're a lucky man, Javi.
为什么这么说
And why's that?
你的家人
Your family.
你知道我从没真正有过家庭
You know, I really never had one.
我爸爸在我五岁的时候走了
My dad left when I was 5,
妈妈为了维持家用要打两份工
and mom had two jobs just to keep the lights on.
我后悔的事很多  哈维
I have a lot of regrets, Javi --
错误的选择
bad choices,
做过的妥协
compromises I made...
选择的路
the path I took.
如果一切都能不一样
If things would have been different,
我们现在已经有了我们自己的家庭
we'd have had a family of our own by now.
如果
If...
本来会很美好的
It would have been good.
我得送你回去了
I better get you back.
我能至少洗个热水澡吗
Can I at least take that hot shower?
拜托
Please?
十分钟
10 minutes, okay?
然后我们就得上路了
And then we got to hit the road.
你可以和我一起来的
You can join me if you want.
我不认为这是个好主意
Uh, I don't -- I don't think that would be a good idea.
我不锁门
I'll leave the door unlocked
以防你改变主意
just in case you change your mind.
真好
Great.
莱恩
Hey, Ryan.
哈维  听我说
Hey, Javi, listen to me.
被害人就是内应
Our victim was the inside man.
他用一次性电话和凶手联系
He communicated with the killer using a burner cell.
我从凶手手机中调出通话记录
I pulled the records from the killer's phone.
我追查了拨出通话
I traced the calls it made.
有三通是打给索尼娅所在的监狱
There were three made to Sonia's prison.
什么  你什么意思
What -- What are you saying?
索尼娅参与了
Sonia was in on it.
不敢相信我会这么蠢
I can't believe I was so stupid.
她耍了我
She played me.
是  她的确耍了你  哥们
Yeah. She sure did, buddy.
凯文  我给你弄了一盘
Kevin, I fixed you your own plate.
谢谢  妈妈
Gracias, Mami.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
兄弟  这可是你妈妈做的莫封戈
Dude, it's your Mom's mofongo.
哪怕是到了世界末日
The whole world could be ending.
我都要狂吃
I'd still be chowing down.
等等  贝克特哪去了
Wait. Where's Beckett?
她不知道  因为要是让她知道
Well, she doesn't know, because if she did...
你就有大麻烦了
...you'd be in deep trouble.
所以我们要在警监发现之前
So we're gonna track your girl down
找到你的妹子
before the Captain finds out.
不  我不能让你为了我这么干
No, I-I-I can't ask you to do that for me.
你不用  我是自愿的
You don't have to. I'm volunteering.
好吧  咱们来好好回想一下
All right? So let's turn your brain back on.
如果索尼娅和凶手有联络
If Sonia was communicating with the killer
并且她精心地设计  让这起押运车抢劫
and she orchestrated this whole armored car heist
和之前害她入狱的那起一模一样
to look exactly like the one she went to prison for,
算好了我们会去找她谈话
knowing that we'd go to talk to her...
索尼娅出狱后就会引我们找到乔伊
Then Sonia would get out and lead us to Joey,
那人拔枪之后她就可以逃走
who pulled a gun so she could run away.
这整件事就是她和乔伊
The whole thing was an escape plan
事前设计好的逃脱计划
that she set up with Joey beforehand.
索尼娅很不幸被我们逮住了
Unfortunately for Sonia, we ran her down.
好吧  假设的确如此  为什么现在搞
Okay, assuming all this is true, why now?
她还有三个月就可以假释了
I mean, she had three months left until parole.
为什么要前功尽弃呢
Why throw that all away?
我不知道
I don't know.
但我敢说乔伊知道
But I bet you Joey does.
我不知道你们在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
我们查了你的财务状况  乔伊
We pulled your financials, Joey.
原来鸡鸡鸡店
You know, it turns out that Chicken-Chicken-Chicken
现在是破产破产破产店
is bankrupt, bankrupt, bankrupt.
我在进行企业重组
I'm doing some corporate restructuring.
好吗  这不是犯罪
All right? That's no crime.
我们还发现给被害人打过电话的
We also found a pair of phone calls to your phone
一次性手机还给你打过电话
from the same burner phone that called our victim.
这样一来  你就是谋杀从犯
Now, that makes you an accessory to murder.
好吧
Okay.
我接到了一通电话  那人我从没见过
I got a phone call from a guy that I never met.
说他知道我有麻烦了
Said he knew I was in trouble,
他提出帮我摆脱困境
and he offered to bail me out.
那要花多少钱
How much would that take?
五十万
Half a million.
抢银行捞到的钱远远不够这个数
They didn't get a fraction of that from the bank job.
索尼娅的那份金子  我们一直没找到
Sonia's share of the gold -- we never found it.
也许她就是为了这个逃走的
Maybe that's why she broke out.
但为什么是现在
But, again, why now?
三个月后  钱还在原地啊
That money will still be there in three months.
游戏结束了乔伊
Play time's over, Joey.
你最好告诉我们这个人是谁
You better tell us who this guy is,
要不你就要住进一间两米四的小牢房
or you're gonna be living in an eight-foot cell
直到你被放进一米八的盒子里抬出来
until they carry you out in a six-foot box.
我发誓我说的是真话
I swear I'm telling the truth.
好吧  我只知道是她一个前男友
All right, all I know is that he was an ex-boyfriend.
我不认识索尼娅的任何一个前男友
I don't know any of Sonia's ex-boyfriends.
你去看看能否查到任何一个的身份
Why don't you see if you can I.D. any of them?
同时  我去查看监狱访客记录
Meanwhile, I'll pull visitor logs from the prison.
好吧
All right.
是贝克特
It's Beckett.
-警监  -进展如何
- Hey, Captain.  - Hey. How's it going?
很好  在追查线索
Fine. Just running down leads.
嗯  哈维坚持得住吧
Uh-huh. And how's Javi holding up?
他不怎么样
Well, he's been better.
知道吗  我明天要
Well, you know what? I'll bring some cronuts
带些可颂圈去
by in the morning.
通常都能让他高兴起来
That usually cheers him up.
好  我们回头见  再见
Okay, I'll talk to you soon. Bye.
一切都好吗
Everything all right?
我不知道  但愿如此
I don't know. I hope so.
-这能让你好起来  -谢谢
- This'll make it better. - Thank you.
我得说  凯瑟琳
I have to say, Katherine,
有你在家真好
it is so good to have you home.
-谢谢  -我支持这项动议
- Thank you. - I second that motion.
谢谢你
Oh, thank you.
露西  这什么鬼
Lucy! What the hell?
快关掉
Turn it off!
凯特  注意措辞
Whoa, language, Kate.
有问题吗
Is there a problem?
说真的吗
Oh, really?
那就让我补偿你一下吧
Well, then, let me make it up to you.
是不是有点极端呢
Isn't that a little extreme?
不  其实  我不这么觉着
No. No, actually, I-I-I don't think so.
这可能听上去有点怪
Look, uh, this -- this might sound odd,
但是自打我回来后  露西就好像在吃醋
but ever since I got back, it's like Lucy's been jealous.
她是"它"  一个塑料金字塔里的中央处理器
She's an "It." A CPU wrapped in a plastic pyramid.
她没有感情的
She doesn't have emotions,
她更不可能会吃醋
and she certainly can't be jealous.
你说什么来着
You were saying?
你告诉我  她过去一年中
So -- So, you're telling me she's only had
只有一人探视
one visitor in the last year?
好吧  叫什么名字
All right, what's the name?
阿伯托·佩纳
Alberto Pena.
好的  谢谢
All right, thanks.
你可真是个大龄男友啊
Whoa, you're an old-ass boyfriend.
不是吧
No.
你是索尼娅的父亲
You're Sonia's father.
詹金斯  你见到埃斯波西托了吗
Hey, Jenkins, have you seen Esposito?
是的  他十分钟之前冲出去了
Yeah, he ran out of here 10 minutes ago.
喂
Yeah?
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
我不能再让你为我冒险了  兄弟
I can't let you put yourself out there for me anymore, bro.
是我的烂摊子  我自己来收拾
This is my mess, and I got to clean it up.
好吧  所有人停下手里的活儿
All right. Everybody stop!
我需要知道埃斯波西托出去之前
I need to know what Esposito found out
查到了什么
when he ran out of here.
拜托  这事生死攸关
Please, it's a matter of life and death.
索尼娅  离开床边
Sonia! Get away from the bed!
我爸爸快不行了  抱歉我没有告诉你
My Dad, he's dying. I'm sorry I didn't tell you.
停下
Just stop it.
我不相信你说的任何事
I'm not buying any of it.
你越狱可不是单单是
You didn't break out of prison
因为你爸快死了
just because your old man was kicking the bucket.
你那份金子在他那儿
He has your share of the gold.
当你得知他中风了
When you found out he had a stroke,
你慌了神  因为你担心
you panicked because you were worried
他的新老婆会偷走你的金子
that his new wife was gonna steal your gold.
有一点我不明白  你怎么不
The thing I don't get is, why didn't you just have
让你在外面的同伙替你拿走
your partner on the outside get it for you?
你不知道在哪
You don't know where it is.
吉米·桑切斯不是"大白鲨"
Jimmy Sanchez wasn't Great White.
你爸爸才是
Your father is.
你入狱后他还留着你那份金子
And he kept your share of the gold after you went in.
哈维  你一直都聪明过头了
Javi, Javi, you were always too smart for your own good.
纽约警局
NYPD!
简直不敢相信你们俩
I can't believe the two of you
竟然把我蒙在鼓里
kept me in the dark about this.
警监  对不起
Captain, I'm sorry.
别说这个  回头再找你们算账
No. We will talk about this later.
现在  我们专心找埃斯波
Right now, let's just focus on finding Espo.
我只希望不会太迟
I just hope it's not too late.
如果索尼娅和她同伙想杀掉埃斯波西托
If Sonia and her partner wanted to kill Esposito,
他们在这就动手了
they would have done it here.
他们留着他一定有什么目的
No, t-they must need him for something.
问题是索尼娅为什么那么着急
The question is, why was Sonia so desperate
想在她父亲死前来见他
to see her father before he died?
埃斯波说他们关系也没有那么亲近
According to Espo, they weren't even that close.
或许他手里有她想要的东西
Maybe he has something she wanted.
我想我知道那是什么了
And I think I know what it is.
金子
Gold.
他手里有她九年前那次抢劫的分赃
He was holding her cut of the heist from nine years ago.
索尼娅不希望金子的下落
Sonia didn't want the secret of the gold's location
随她父亲之死而消失
to die with her father.
他们带走埃斯波西托是怕我们阻止他们
They took Esposito for insurance in case we tried to stop them.
找到佩纳藏金币的地方就能找到埃斯波
Which means we find Pena's coin stash, we'll find Espo.
问题是  我们对这个人什么都不知道
Problem is, we don't know the first thing about this guy.
只能突击一下了  把这个地方好好找找
Well, time for a crash course. Let's tear this place apart.
哈维  你醒了吗
Javi, you awake?
你脑袋怎么样
How's your head?
我没事
I'm fine.
你那小白脸打人就跟个娘们似的
Your boy toy hits like a little bitch.
对不起  哈维
You know, I'm sorry, Javi.
事情不该像现在这样
It wasn't supposed to go like this.
不该有人为此受到伤害
No one was meant to get hurt.
别说伤不伤害  今天两个孩子失去了父亲
Forget hurt -- Two little kids don't have a dad today
就因为你跟你的男朋友
because of you and your boyfriend.
你不要觉得我对此无动于衷
Don't think that's not tearing me up.
你必须相信我  哈维
You have to believe me, Javi.
我不知道罗纳尔多会杀掉那个人
I didn't know Ronaldo was gonna kill that man.
这个借口也太蹩脚了
That is such a cop-out.
你知道他能干出什么事
You knew what he was capable of.
我只是没想到你竟然会这么做
I just didn't think that you were.
我以为你内心深处是个好人
I thought that, deep down, you had a good heart.
我知道你小时候日子过得很艰难
I know that you had a tough go when you were little,
但迟早你都得从童年的阴影里走出来
but sooner or later, you got to stop blaming your childhood.
到了一定时候  当你选择了做错事
At some point, when you choose wrong over right...
就得怨你自己
that's on you.
你一直都这么黑白分明
It's always been so black-and-white with you, huh?
埃斯波的生活准则
Espo's rules of life.
那好  我来跟你说说
Well, let me tell you something.
九年来  我一直待在牢房里
I spent nine years in that cell
而乔伊和我爸爸却逍遥法外
while Joey and my dad breathed free air
花大钱享乐
and spent their millions.
我只有钱这一个念想
All I had to hold on to was the money.
我绝对不会对此放手的
No way in hell I was gonna let that go.
前面就到了
This is it up ahead.
我希望那些钱值得你这么做
Well, I hope that money's worth it,
因为你这一辈子
'cause you're gonna have to live with what you've done
都要承受良心的谴责
for the rest of your life.
你真该对女士友善一点
You should really be nicer to the lady.
但她的心软并不会救你一命
Not that her little soft spot's gonna save you,
等我们拿到了金子...
'cause once we get that gold...
索尼娅的父亲拥有至少六家生意
Sonia's dad owned at least half a dozen businesses --
干洗店  洗车店  还有一家古巴餐馆
dry cleaners, car wash, a Cuban restaurant?
都是资金流动大的地方  说得通
All high cash flow. Makes sense.
如果他要一点一点把金子变现
If he was selling off his gold bit by bit,
他需要地方来洗钱
he'd need a place to launder the money.
根据这家公司的银行记录
Well, according to the company's bank records,
每周的收入汇款都很一致
the weekly receipts were pretty uniform.
除了  快看这个  干洗店
Except, look at this, the dry cleaners --
大概三个月前  周存款金额
about three months ago, there was a spike
数量猛增
in the weekly deposit amount
三个月前还有再前三个月都是
and three months before that and before that.
餐馆也是一样
Same with the restaurant.
所以他每三个月都会去拿一部分金子
So he was retrieving some of the gold every three months,
卖掉之后通过他的生意
selling it off, and then running the proceeds
把收入转进来
through his businesses.
莱恩  维克拉姆在佩纳手机里
Hey, Ryan, where is Vikram
找到定位信息了吗
with the GPS info from Pena's phone?
他刚发过来
He just sent this over.
佩纳大部分时间都在家附近活动
Pena stayed close to home most of the time,
除了这个位置
except for this location.
看着很异常
Looks to be an outlier.
他不经常去那  只会每...
He wouldn't go there often, only once every --
每三月去一次
Every three months?
的确  而且只在晚上
Exactly. And only at night.
那里有什么
And what's there?
看一下
Let's see, uh...
一个旧爱迪生联合电力公司的储存设施
It's an old Con Ed storage facility.
简直是用来藏匿金币的好地方
Perfect place for stashing coins.
佩纳有一家运输公司
Pena owned a transport company
跟爱迪生联合电力公司签有外包合同
that subcontracts with Con Ed.
就是这了  他就在那
Then that's it. That's where he is.
我们走  一旦他们找到了金子
Let's go. Once they find the gold,
他们就要逃跑了
they're gonna make a run for it.
而且要先杀掉埃斯波
After they kill Espo.
你们应该去自首
You guys should just turn yourselves in.
即使你们带着金子逃走了
Even if you do get away with the gold,
你们不论走到哪里我的同事都能找到你们
there's no place you can go where my guys won't find you.
也许吧
Well, maybe.
但跟你比起来我还是觉得我的胜算大得多
But I like my odds a lot more than yours right now.
她说金子就在上面
She said it would be up there.
你去吧
You go up.
我在这看着他
I'll stay here with him.
小心点  宝贝
Careful, baby.
自从我向你求婚以后
Haven't seen you smile like that
好久没看你这样笑了
since I gave you the ring.
闭嘴
Shut up.
都过去好久了  不是吗
Seems so long ago, doesn't it?
那是另一辈子了
It was a different life.
你要干嘛
What are you doing?
我们不能带着金子同时还要看着他
We can't carry the gold and watch him at the same time.
所以他的故事就在这里结束了
So this is where his story ends.
不行
No.
得了吧  宝贝
Come on, babe.
不要装得好像你不知道
Don't even pretend like you didn't know
事情会像这样发展
it was gonna go down this way.
要是不想看就转过身去
Turn away if you don't want to see it.
你在搞什么
What the hell?
我不能让你这么做
I can't let you do that.
我们没时间来争这个
We don't have time for this.
他得死  我们得走了
He's got to die, and we got to go.
不行  我们就把他留在这里  留活口
No. We leave him here alive.
他是你前未婚夫  他把你抛弃了
He was your fiancé? And he threw you away.
他任凭你在监狱里自生自灭
He left you to rot in prison.
是我陪在你身边
I was the one who was there for you.
为什么你宁愿打我  也要保护他
So, why are you willing to shoot me save him?
因为我爱他
Because I love him.
停下  哈维  哈维
Stop, Javi. Javi!
哈维  够了
Javi, stop!
都结束了  索尼娅
It's over, Sonia.
不
No.
我不回去  我做不到
I won't go back. I can't.
你做得到
You can.
你也会回去的
And you will.
九年前  我发现你是个贼
Nine years ago, I found out you were a thief.
你知道当时我做了什么吗
You know what I did then?
知道
Yeah.
-你把我逮捕了  -不
- You arrested me. - No.
我回到家里收拾行李
I went home, and I packed a bag.
拿了护照
And then I grabbed my passport,
取出全部存款
cleared out my savings account.
我准备抛弃自己所信仰的一切
I was ready to abandon everything I believed in...
因为我无法想象没有你的人生
...because I couldn't picture a life without you.
你为什么没这么做
Why didn't you?
我是个警察  索尼娅  我
I'm a cop, Sonia. I --
这是我唯一的梦想
It's all I ever wanted to be.
如果我丢掉这一切的话
If I threw that away,
我没办法配得上你
then I wouldn't even deserve you.
我们有机会重新开始  哈维
We've got a second chance, Javi.
我们可以现在私奔  就和当年一样
We can run now. It can be like it was.
不
No.
过去再也回不去了
It can never be like it was.
如果我能坚强起来  迈出这一步
If I was strong enough to walk up those steps
逮捕我今生的挚爱
and arrest the love of my life,
你也可以坚强起来  面对即将发生的一切
then you are strong enough to face what comes next.
纽约警局
NYPD!
你没事吧  搭档
You okay, partner?
没事
Yeah.
转过身去
Turn around.
-走吧  -好
- Let's go. - All right.
请让我来
Please.
对不起  我搞砸了
I'm sorry. I screwed up.
我因为对索尼娅的感情而影响了判断力
I let my feelings for Sonia cloud my judgment,
放松了警惕
and -- and I let my guard down.
听着  我不会假装
I -- Look, I'm not gonna pretend
自己没犯过同样的错误
that I haven't done the same thing,
但是我现在是警监了
but I am captain now.
所以我必须让你停职一周  没有工资
So I have to suspend you for a week -- no pay.
遵命  长官
Yes, ma'am.
你的决定是正确的
You did the right thing.
能让我们聊几句吗
Can you give us a sec?
我和地方检察官谈过了  等一切尘埃落定
So, uh, I talked to the D.A., and when the dust settles,
如果你出庭指证罗纳尔多
he's willing to let you plead out as an accessory
他愿意以从犯身份给你轻判
if you testify against Ronaldo.
还要判几年
How many more years?
至少两年
At least two.
这次你会来探监吗
Are you gonna come visit me this time?
会的
Yeah.
你会给我送里面藏着锉刀的蛋糕吗
Are you gonna bring me a cake with a file in it?
应该不会
Probably not.
谢天谢地  你没谢顶
Thank God you didn't go bald.
我正想对你说这个呢
I was just thinking the same thing about you.
多保重  索尼娅
Take care of yourself, Sonia.
你也一样
You, too.
我们很快就会再见面的
I'll see you soon.
但愿如此
I hope so.
你接下来要怎么办
So, what are you gonna do now?
不知道
I don't know.
今天我不用继续上班了
Turns out I got the rest of the day free.
我也是  我请病假了
Yeah, me too. I, uh, just called in sick.
我们去一醉方休吧
Let's go get really drunk.
正合我意
Damn straight.
终于到家了
Home at last,
完美的一夜已经万事俱备
with all the makings of a perfect evening --
泰式料理  一瓶皮诺  还有我最爱的两个姑娘
Thai food, a bottle of Pino, and my two favorite ladies.
等等  两个姑娘
Wait, two?
这是在说我的双峰吗
Is that a joke about my boobs?
我当然是指  你和露西了
I'm referring, of course, to you and Lucy.
对啊  露西
Oh, right. Lucy.
拜托  别生气啊  我开玩笑的
Oh, come on, don't be mad. I'm kidding.
现在再说是你的双峰是不是太晚了
Is -- Is it too late to say it's about your boobs?
没关系的
No. It's -- It's fine.
实际上  那天是我反应过度了
The truth is, is that I overreacted the other day.
我感觉从现在开始
I have a feeling that Lucy and I are gonna be
我和露西的关系会好起来了
on much better terms from here on out.
你这么说我真开心
And I am glad to hear it.
听见了吗  露西
You hear that, Lucy?
我就知道你会赢得她的芳心
I knew you'd win her over.
现在  麻烦你帮我们
Now, why don't you dim the lights for us
把灯光调暗点
just a little bit?
这样如何  里克
How's that, Rick?
灯光不合你的心意吗
A-Are the lights not to your satisfaction?
没事  灯光挺好的
No, they're fine.
只是  你是谁  露西去哪了
Just, uh, who are you, and where's Lucy?
我叫莱纳斯
My name's Linus,
我开始觉得你不喜欢我了
and I'm starting to think you don't like me.
很好  真有意思  你做了什么
Oh, okay, very funny. What did you do?
我读了使用说明  显然
I-I read the user's manual, and, apparently,
只要轻轻点一个键
with the simple flick of a switch,
姑娘就会变成小伙子了
she can become a he.
你把露西杀了
You killed Lucy?
没有  我没杀她  她还在里面呢
No. I didn't kill her. I mean, she's still in there.
怎么了
Why?
你想把她换回来
You want her back?
不是  当然不是
No. Of course not.
不用  不用  就用莱纳斯好了
No. No. Linus it is.
好吧
All right, good.
我要去换衣服了
Well, I'm gonna go change,
你们两个熟悉一下吧
so why don't you guys become acquainted?
好吧
All right.
莱纳斯  我们开始这段兄弟情吧
Okay, Linus. Let's get this bromance started.
给我来一杯卡布奇诺怎么样
How about you make me a little cappuccino?
这么晚了喝咖啡因不好  里克
It's a little late for caffeine, Rick.
来一段伸展瑜伽睡前放松一下怎么样
How about some relaxing yoga stretches before bed?
实验结束了
And experiment's over.
那个键在哪里
Where's that switch?
莱纳斯  你电击我
Linus, you gave me a little shock.
我觉得你是不是短路了之类的
I think you must have a short or something.
我不喜欢被人摸  里克
I don't like to be touched, Rick.
总之不喜欢被你摸
Not by you, anyway.
贝克特
Beckett!